I don't ever slow up no I don't take
I got no love for the fness if you
want to play tough and want to hate this
although show up I don't have a slow up
no I don't take I got no love for
the fiess if you want to play tough and
want to hate this I'll always show up
and make a statement I don't have slow
up no I don't take I got no love
for the fakeess if you want to play
tough and want to hate this I'll always
show up and make a state everything I do
so instinctive and so passionate every
word I move so descriptive like an
adjective I got a vetta against people
who patented it being negative when you
should be getting after it I got facts
over facts over tracks this a n spitting
slow spitting fast I a roast I could gas
think I'm okay Al last but I don't know
if that can erase all the past and the
pettiness a reflection of The Emptiness
hilarious you think you're with my time
you're Delirious mysterious because you
right behind the fake exterior inferior
you know we always be a bit super ior
get off of me this ain't no humble brag
I want you to hear words you can say
them back I want you to feel free from
the chains and last and to believe in
what you got it was built to last yeah
now that I've been put through hell I
never got anyone's hell I had to do it
all
myself I don't never slow up no I don't
take I've got no love for the
fakeess if you want to play tough and
want to hate this I'll always show up
and make a statement I don't have slow
up no I don't take I've got no love
for the fness if you want to play tough
and want to hate this I'll always show
up and make a statement going to learn
the consequence of being incompetent
mental health is confidence dreams into
some hestness I'm not here to say the
day that's for you to take away I could
play a million mind games but instead of
say something not logical something that
is topical rub it on and watch it go
make yourself Unstoppable Dre are
irresponsible but they're always
possible if you just believe you be so
remarkable thoughts in my head a collage
in they spread I'll be great one day
going off of my meds no I'm not giving
up no I'm not giv in I will make it to
the top taking off you know when I got
to make it I'm saving every day to taste
it I'm patient put my mind ni can Ary
take it I'm chasing a dream that I've
had for several ages of bacing modern
Kingdom for the
Tak now that I've been put through out I
never got anyone's help I have to do it
all myself
I don't never scow up no I don't take
I got no